Hello hi good morning Sat Sri Akaal adab
ahead I was busy with your own business but I thought of returning home that I have
brought the same good news in your opinion, you must be fed up of listening to the song, I have
said it many times that I will try but I have brought a
new song
but tell me today's good news it is my duty
but wait for a minute because I am
back in 2 minutes to tell you the truth, do it yes yes so I
am Lakhan Amit Kalra and I will bring
whose good news how many cases can be told that the number of cases is
continuously decreasing and
how come around 91 thousand 1.35 lakh have
recovered how are active how around
11 lakh there have been 3412 deaths
yesterday 6th August so don't even ask what happened
Bihar had given a big shock and one
big thing has come to light that if we
mute this second count from March 1, 2021 then there have been
more than two lakh deaths, the web portal
also got 62 training of deaths in seconds and
how come 60% of all the deaths came in seconds  Just
think how dangerous the numbers are and there have been
more than 2 lakh deaths. In terms of deaths,
we in India are at number one in the world.
Brazil is at number one. Wherever it is, it will
give us 2.5 lakh. This is Dudhola, the
total deaths have happened around Dudhola.
Brazil is number one in India, after that,
we are at number one in
terms of total deaths. Then Brazil,
then we are number one somewhere.
Indians will be at the forefront. But friend,
I did not want to go further in this today, but
now what can we do, our fate, Universe,
Delta, Alpha, everyone has messed it up,
let me tell you very quickly, half of the entire state,
12,000 in Maharashtra, how will it
deepen in Karnataka, apart from this, 14, how
Tamil Nadu, how vouchers of 16,000 in Bandra, how
5000 in banks, how 596 in UP, how
305 in Delhi, how ready in Chhattisgarh, how
500 in Rajasthan, how
6000 in Odisha, how there were 544 in Gujarat,
in MP, more than that, 539 in Haryana, how
in Bihar  23 with 551 is
directly in Bihar on 23-04-2012 in my Bihar Tamil Nadu is
1763 in Punjab 13 how in Jharkhand 293 how
in Uttarakhand 388 how this
was in the whole of India I have
told you all the things now let me talk first tell me about
Mumbai we are magnetic Mumbai my Mumbai
how much to tell Airtel how in Mumbai
660 how 22 wins have been made so the death toll is continuously
decreasing Kolkata I have
not come to know the name is Kolkata 485 how to go
24 we are like this Bhalo Bashi one
line I don't know anything beyond this let's go
Misti Misti Mishti Doi and Delhi Delhi Delhi Delhi Delhi Delhi Delhi
and Delhi Delhi Delhi Delhi Ho Delhi Ho Delhi
Delhi 305
members 44000 are posted point on the phone
around 75 thousand tests were done so it was felt that the
danger in Delhi's cases are decreasing
and there is good news in Delhi that the
Delhi government is going to set up the 19th oxygen plant, it is a
matter of great happiness but
further  I am going to tell you some more things that are coming, I am
sure they are related to it, there are some other things too,
so listen to the full video. You have just
heard the good news, the wind has
not started, this is also the next good news is that till now there was a
problem in the railways that
restrictions were imposed in big cities in the country,
artificial vaccines were being used, so
many people did not pay attention, now
IRCTC should also take its share, it is a
very good share, IRCTC has said,
now if you have the vaccine certificate, then the more
you get the artificial vaccine,
show your vaccination setting, anyway,
show it to the one who comes out, then this will
also become easier, the one who gets the vaccine will get the
artificial vaccine, everything is a
good thing, isn't it? And one more good news has come,
Baba Ramdev said that he will also get the vaccine, well, better late than never,
look, Baba
is like you, your fight may be with allopathic,
your fight may be with the other version,
but you can afford to fight with the vaccine
because we have not made the vaccine and whether
we die from the vaccine or not, that is our
job, but speaking against the vaccine or
making fun of the vaccine is against the country.  To make fun of, to make
fun of the government of the country, so
now better late than never, you said I will do it
that way and yoga will also work along with it, there is a
double door, is there any doubt that yoga
meditation should be number one,
I also believe that yoga has a huge
role in it, in the end I will say thank you to Ramdev
Baba Ji or your yoga guru and he
spread his yoga, that's enough, the rest is
super, okay, so thank you Baba
Ramdev Ji and I should also praise you, the
doctors who saved my life, that is Rover Evoque,
they have done a great job, I do
n't have any fight, allopathy doctors are a very
good thing, Ramdev Ji, thank you very much,
I was part of you, what should I do, I am going to
buy Soya Ruchi Soya shares, that's all I
can do for you, now let's come to some
vaccine, there is news about the vaccine, the
Affair vaccine will be available
in India for Rs.730, whereas it will be available at half the rate
in the US, it is Rs.14 in America, it is around Rs.15 in the UK, it will be
available in India at half the rate,
this is the third story, okay, so thank you, figure and
one  And the vaccine is also in the pipeline, it will be available
around January 2022.
India is in talks with all of them
for 200 million dollars. 50
million for Pfizer, 70 million for Johnson &
Johnson, 50 million for Modena vaccine.
Two
separate talks are going on, but Johnson &
Johnson's is a single-dose vaccine, so it is a zinc-
dose vaccine, so that means 140% of it will be doubled,
where it will go, the remaining 20% ​​of
Johnson & Johnson's will be given only one, so it
can cover to a great extent. Therefore,
Sanjay Junction is a little ahead in this matter, it is a
single-dose vaccine compared to other vaccines.
Okay, so this was today's good news, and I will
tell you about 119 rolls in the next video. The
guidelines related to treatment and wearing masks in children have changed. So,
if I make a video, I will
tell you. Take a little oath. And that's it.
Now don't abuse, friend.
Stop coming here and checking anyone.
This is the BJP's plan heading. Don't think about it.  There
is politics in Bihar, you
said that you want to go into politics, it is
not in everyone's capacity to hear the truth and no
government is clean, be it
BJP, be it of the
Aam Aadmi Party, be it of Congress, be it of
any third party, be it
Mamata Banerjee, no
government is clean, neither are
all those sitting in that government or Munmun Party
clean, but still everyone is contributing for the country, so whatever I
say,
I speak from my heart, I never
speak thinking
whose government is there, whose is not, yesterday the
truth of Bihar's education was to be brought, so I
brought it in front of my dear ones, we had
already made our guesses, now
after this, if there is Sachan, then there is going to be a person from UP,
we are from Rajasthan, where so many doctors died, then
why are they not standing there,
gradually I think everyone will audit
this update, you will revise it, it
may come, this is just the beginning of Bihar
because otherwise then our public interest will be taken care of.  Petitions will be
filed Ujjain hit, I am leaving,
thank you very much and then I will just say that take
care of yourself and still do not
relax the rules of safety and before leaving I will say as much as possible that we have to keep going, we
are travelers, we do not know if we will reach our destination,
our only job is to keep going
and if this virus reaches the channel again, then
pigeon go go pigeon go go pigeon go go pigeon go
-go-ja
first letter of first love Om in the first letter of first love, have
mercy on China, don't gather the garlands,
mercy China, hurry up, the garlands have made my
mind go crazy and we are all very tired,
very tight and the sooner we go, the
better, thank you very much, you were able to
calculate your total, it has happened